Guide to the Anne Ramsay Somers Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1948-2006; Accession 2007-M-098
  - Topical
    - Joint Commission Long Term Care Accreditation, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 246)
    - Haverford College, 1986-1999 (Box 4, Folder 247)
    - Hanley, John J. (CCRC), circa 1988 (Box 4, Folder 248)
    - United Senior Action, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 249)
    - Advisory Council on Education for Health, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 250)
    - Pennsylvania health care, circa 1972-1994 (Box 4, Folder 251)
    - American Public Health Association (APHA), circa 1979 (Box 4, Folder 252)
    - American Hospital Association (AHA), 1980-1987 (Box 4, Folder 253)
    - Health education, 1980-1990 (Box 4, Folder 254)
    - Center for Disease Control, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 255)
    - Preventive medicine, circa 1970-1995 (Box 4, Folder 256 - 257)
    - Bibliography and sources of data, 1965-1993 (Box 4, Folder 258)
    - Bradley, Bill, U.S. Senate, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 259)
    - Civil rights, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 260)
    - Health Maintenance Organizations (HMO), 1958-1990 (Box 4, Folder 261)
    - International Center for Development Policy, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 262)
    - Interview with Anne Somers by A. J. Vogl, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 263)
    - Latin America, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 264)
    - Marriott Senior Living Services, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 265)
    - Medical leaders, 1969-1990 (Box 5, Folder 266)
    - Medicare, 1983-1988 (Box 5, Folder 267)
    - Medicare reform proposals, 1983-1995 (Box 5, Folder 268)
    - National health reform correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 269)
    - Patients' Bill of Rights, 1973-1987 (Box 5, Folder 270)
    - Preventive medicine training, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 271)
    - Princeton continuing care retirement communities (CCRC), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 272)
    - Technological and industrial society, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 273)
    - Youth corps, 1972-1987 (Box 5, Folder 274)
    - Teaching geriatric medicine, 1983-1988 (Box 5, Folder 275)
    - U.S. Senate aging committee, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 276)
    - Prevention, general, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 277)
    - Aging in New Jersey, 1981-1986 (Box 5, Folder 278)
    - Abuse and neglect of the elderly, 1983-1992 (Box 5, Folder 279)
    - Aging Network News, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 280)
    - American Association of Retired Persons (AARP), 1987-1995 (Box 5, Folder 281)
    - American College of Physicians ACP Observer, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 282)
    - Medical history, 1959-1984 (Box 5, Folder 283)
    - Journals, 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 284)
    - Managed care, 1989-1995 (Box 5, Folder 285)
    - Technical revolution in medicine, 1980-1988 (Box 5, Folder 286)
    - Proposed Commission on Long-Term Care Financing, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 287)
    - Department of Veteran's Affairs, 1987-1993 (Box 5, Folder 288)
    - Costs and cost controls, 1990-1996 (Box 5, Folder 289)
    - Bioethics, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 290)
    - Hospital mergings, 1966-1995 (Box 5, Folder 291)
    - Hospitals, 1987-1995 (Box 5, Folder 292)
    - Consumer health education, 1971-1988 (Box 5, Folder 293)
    - University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 294)
    - University of Pennsylvania Institute on Aging, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 295)
    - American health centers, 1961-1995 (Box 5, Folder 296)